equibase.com 2019-04-15

# Equibase | Privacy Policy

### PRIVACY STATEMENT FOR _equibase.com_

**Please Note:** This privacy policy was last updated on March 27, 2019 and is subject to future change without notice.

Equibase Company LLC has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: **_equibase.com_**.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. We monitor access to the site via IP address for data scrapers and automated access of information on the site. We block IP addresses engaging in these activities.

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes. Some of the ads you receive on Web pages are customized based on predictions about your interests generated from your visits to different Websites in this browser and on other devices you may use. To opt out of interest based advertising from specific participating companies, or from all participating companies, [click here](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN). You can learn more about certain types of targeted advertising by visiting the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/). 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and e-mail address) and basic demographic information. We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company and the Thoroughbred racing industry. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the Opt Out Procedures for Mailings section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. Further, Equibase may occasionally provide, sell, or rent limited user data to third parties, including companies that offer products and services for sale to Equibase’s users. This limited data includes names, job titles, companies/organizations, and business addresses, but do not include business phone numbers or business fax numbers.

Aggregate demographic information collected via use of the site may be shared with advertisers and other partners. This aggregate information is not traceable to an individual user.

When registering at our site, your registration information is also sent to TrackMaster, a wholly-owned subsidiary of Equibase Company LLC so that your registration information can be used to purchase products and services at their website **_trackmaster.com_**. It will be necessary for you to complete additional registration information at **_trackmaster.com_** before being able to make purchases at that site. No additional registration information is required to make purchases at _**equibase.com**_. Products and services on **_trackmaster.com_** are covered by a separate set of Terms and Conditions that will be provided for your approval before any purchases can be made. Registration at our web site does not obligate you to make purchases at **_trackmaster.com_**. Any questions concerning the terms and conditions for the **_trackmaster.com_** web site should be referred to TrackMaster via the contact information provide via that site.

This site contains links to other sites. **_equibase.com_** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. Billing is processed at the time of purchase, unless you have reached customer account status, at which time your card will be billed at the end of the month for purchases made during that month. Monthly account billing will continue until the visitor notifies Equibase Company in writing or if the monthly billing process fails, at which time billing for all future purchases will be processed at the time of purchase.

### Security

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. **_equibase.com_** uses 128-bit encryption for all secure links, which adheres to Federal and International guidelines for secure server transactions. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Equibase uses Tokenization of payment card information and does not keep, maintain or transmit payment card data.

_**equibase.com**_ is tested and certified daily to pass the McAfee Secure Security Scan. To help address concerns about possible hacker access to your confidential data, and the safety of visiting _**equibase.com**_ , the "live" McAfee Secure mark appears only when this site passes the daily McAfee Secure tests.

### Opt Out Procedures for Mailings

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from Equibase Company and third parties at the point where we request registration information about the visitor.

This site gives users the option for removing their information from our database to not receive information about Equibase Products and Services. In order to complete this request, the User must send a written request via e-mail, including their Customer ID to: [Equibase Mailing List Removal](mailto:registration@equibase.com?subject=Equibase%20Mail%20List%20Remove)

This site gives users the option to no longer receive the Equibase Inside Track mailing. In order to complete this request, the User must send a written request via e-mail, from the e-mail address used at registration, to: [Inside Track Removal](mailto:insidetrack@equibase.com?subject=Inside%20Track%20Remove)

This site gives users the option to de-activate their Virtual Stable. In order to complete this request, the User can do so from the [Virtual Stable Main Page](http://www.equibase.com/virtual/gvsVirtualStableMain.cfm?SID=1), or by sending a written request via e-mail, from the e-mail address used for the Virtual Stable, to: [De-activate Virtual Stable](mailto:feedback@equibase.com?subject=De-activate%20Virtual%20Stable)

### Contacting the web site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact

Shelby Cook   
Online Services Coordinator   
Equibase Company LLC   
821 Corporate Drive   
Lexington, KY 40503   
1-800-333-2211   
scook@equibase.com
